{
    "q1": {
                "question": "Brazil belongs to?",
                "options": [
                    "Africa",
                    "North_America",
                    "Europe",
                    "South_America"
                ],
                "answer": "South_America"
            },
    "q2": {
                "question": "National animal of Australia?",
                "options": [
                    "Lion",
                    "Tiger",
                    "Kangaroo",
                    "Panther"
                ],
                "answer": "Kangaroo"
            },
    
    "q3": {
                "question": "What is the fastest animal alive?",
                "options": [
                    "Peregrine_Falcon",
                    "Cheetah",
                    "Sailfish",
                    "Dragonfly"
                ],
                "answer": "Peregrine_Falcon"
            },
    "q4": {
                "question": "Light travels at its fastest in?",
                "options": [
                    "Vacuum",
                    "Salt_water",
                    "Air_at_0Â°C",
                    "Drizzle"
                ],
                "answer":"Vacuum"
            },
    "q5": {
                "question": "Number of rings on the Olympic flag?",
                "options": [
                    "4",
                    "6",
                    "5",
                    "3"
                ],
                "answer": "5"
            },
    "q6": {
                "question": "Number of holes on a standard bowling ball?",
                "options": [
                    "4",
                    "6",
                    "5",
                    "3"
                ],
                "answer": "3"
            },
    "q7": {
                "question": "What are the main colors on the flag of Spain?",
                "options": [
                    "Black_and_yellow",
                    "Green_and_white",
                    "Blue_and_white",
                    "Red_and_yellow"
                ],
                "answer": "Red_and_yellow"
            },
    "q8": {
                "question": " What is the longest that an elephant has ever provably lived?",
                "options": [
                    "17_years",
                    "49_years",
                    "86_years",
                    "142_years"
                ],
                "answer": "86_years"
            },
    "q9": {
                "question": "'War and Peace' originally written in?",
                "options": [
                    "Russian",
                    "German",
                    "Spanish",
                    "Portuguese"
                ],
                "answer": "Russian"
            },
    "q10": {
                "question": "Which of these countries was not a Soviet Republic in USSR?",
                "options": [
                    "Azerbaijan",
                    "Kyrgyzstan",
                    "Moldova",
                    "Serbia"
                ],
                "answer": "Serbia"
            }
}












